## Edgard Kozlowski

Designer & Developer

## **Summary**

Designer and Developer, with +4 years of experience designing digital products plus +1 year developing websites. Dealing with complex problems and transforming them into intuitive and easy-to-use designs is the thing that I most like to do. In order to achieve results I always try to find ways to know more about the product stakeholders and create high fidelity prototypes to validate and communicate solutions.

## **Experience**

Developer at TUUT

September 2016 - Present

Partner at Balacoba.co

February 2017 - December 2017

**Product Designer at Emotion.me** 

December 2014 - July 2016

**Designer at Agência Maior** 

May 2013 - July 2014

## **Education**

**UX Weekend at Mergo UX and Usability Courses** 

February 2015 (Fourteen yours)

**English Course at VEC - Vancouver English Centre, Canada** 

August 2014 - October 2014

College in Communication at Centro Universitário de Volta Redonda

January 2009 - June 2012